const questions = [
    {
        question: 'Javascript is an _______ language?',
        options: ['Object-Oriented', 'Object-Based', 'Procedural', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 'Object-Oriented',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?',
        options: ['Var', 'Let', 'None of the above', 'Both Var & Let'],
        answer: 'Both Var & Let',
    },
    {
        question: 'Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?',
        options: ['Throws an error', 'Ignores the statements', 'Gives a warning', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 'Ignores the statements',
    },
    {
        question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
        options: ['const', 'var', 'let', 'none'],
        answer: 'const',
    },
    {
        question: `What will be the output of the following code snippet?
       a = 5 + "9";
       document.write(a);
   `,
        options: ['Compilation Error', '14', 'Runtime Error', '59'],
        answer: '59',
    },
    {
        question: 'How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?',
        options: ['clearInterval', 'clearTimer', 'intervalOver', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 'clearInterval',
    },
    {
        question: 'How do you write a conditional statement for executing some statements only if "i" is equal to 5?',
        options: ['if i = 5', ' if i == 5 then', 'if (i == 5)', 'if i = 5 then'],
        answer: 'if (i == 5)',
    },
    {
        question: 'How do you create a function in JavaScript?',
        options: ['function = myFunction()', ' function:myFunction()', ' function myFunction()', 'create myFunction()'],
        answer: 'function myFunction()',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which method is used to add an element at the end of an array?',
        options: ['array.push(element)', 'array.pop(element)', 'array.unshift(element)', 'array.shift(element)'],
        answer: 'array.push(element)',
    },
    {
        question: 'How can a JavaScript variable be declared conditionally?',
        options: ['var x if (condition)', 'if (condition) var x', ' var x = (condition) ? value1 : value2', 'condition(var x)'],
        answer: ' var x = (condition) ? value1 : value2',
    }
];

